storknet.com 2005-04-03

# StorkNet - The Pregnancy and Parenting Online Community

**Privacy Policy**

StorkNet has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the StorkNet Family of websites, which includes:  
     StorkNetFamily.com  
     StorkNet.com  
     PregnancyGuideOnline.com  
     Exploring Womanhood  
     Married Romance  
     EriChad.com  
     StorkNotes.com

Doerr Consulting is the legal owner of StorkNet and is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will never share, sell, or rent your personal information in ways that are not disclosed in this statement without your consent. Any breach of this policy by our staff will result in immediate dismissal. 

**Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website, monitor site usage and help us collect broad demographic information. Such statistics help us identify popular areas so we can improve the visitor experience.

**Cookies**

The StorkNet message boards (at StorkNotes.com) use cookies so you don't have to re-enter your user name and password each time you visit the boards. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. Cookies are not executable pieces of code and cannot do anything to your hard drive. They are merely pieces of "text" stored on your computer. They are easy to delete from your hard drive (and it's not a bad idea to do this once in awhile).

If you would like to know more about cookies, read the US Government Information Bulletin (I-034) regarding cookie technology at <http://www.ciac.org/ciac/bulletins/i-034.shtml>.

**Advertisers**

We use an outside advertising company to display some of the ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies on our message boards, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad agency, and we do not have access to this info. 

**Message Board Registration**

Our Message Boards require registration to post, and the registration form requires users to give us their name and email. Users have the option to make their email address private or public. If a user opts to make their email public, StorkNet is not responsible for any spam or other email received from visitors to our message boards. Our message board software gives users the ability to "opt-out" of administrative mailings regarding the message board. 

**Public Forums**

StorkNet makes message board forums and email (via StorkNetMail.com) available to its users. Please be aware that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, and care should be exercised when deciding to disclose personal information. StorkNet cannot be responsible for the information users post in these public areas including other websites.

**Email Service**

Users of our free email service are required to complete a personal profile with everyone.net (our email service provider). Please review **[everyone.net's privacy statement](http://www.everyone.net/main/html/p_policy.html)** for more details.

**Surveys and Contests**

From time to time, our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. This information is not shared with any third party. Survey information is used for purposes of monitoring or improving use and satisfaction of StorkNet and your name is not required.

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. StorkNet is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. When you click on a link that takes you off a StorkNet site, this Privacy Policy no longer applies including e-commerce sites listed in the StorkNet Mall.

**Newsletters**

If you subscribe to our Before Birth and Beyond newsletter, you will not receive separate email from other companies as a result of subscribing to our newsletter. Subscribed addresses are not shared or sold with other companies. If you decide to unsubscribe, you may do so via the link provided in the newsletter or going to **<http://www.storknet.com/newsletter>**.

**Send This Page to a Friend Feature**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, the user is asked for the friend's name and email address. StorkNet automatically sends the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. This information is not stored and the friend will never receive another email from StorkNet as a result of this service.

**Contacting StorkNet**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, you may contact:  
Maribeth Doerr  
**sninfo@storknet.com**
